<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>permanent-notes on</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/tags/permanent-notes/</link><description>Recent content in permanent-notes on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/tags/permanent-notes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Active Listening</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/active-listening/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/active-listening/</guid><description>Relevant Notes mental-health Notes Active listening involves consciously paying attention to who you&amp;rsquo;re listening to.</description></item><item><title>Advocacy burnout</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/advocacy-burnout/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/advocacy-burnout/</guid><description>Tags: #permanent-notes Relevant Notes mental-health References LINK IN REFIND: On advocacy by Chloe Abrasada (chloe-abrasada) – Refind How to keep changing the world when you&amp;rsquo;re burning out - makesense Philippines Advocacy Burnout is Real - Girls' Globe How To Avoid Burnout for Sustainable Advocacy How Advocates for Inclusion Keep from Burning Out Breaking the burnout in advocacy | University of Technology Sydney How I (Try to) Avoid Advocacy Burnout | Cancer.</description></item><item><title>Availability bias</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/availability-bias/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/availability-bias/</guid><description>Relevant Notes Notes Believing what&amp;rsquo;s convenient Believing what we connect most to ourself Highlights Availability bias is the tendency to rely on information that’s readily available, instead of what’s actually more relevant to the situation.</description></item><item><title>Avoid being reactive</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/avoid-being-reactive/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/avoid-being-reactive/</guid><description>Tags: #permanent-notes
Relevant Notes
Let go of things that are outside of your control</description></item><item><title>Behavioral segmentation</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/behavioral-segmentation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/behavioral-segmentation/</guid><description>Relevant Notes ux-design Notes Highlights Everything You Need to Know About Behavioral Segmentation [+ Examples] 1 Behavioral segmentation is the process of grouping customers into categories based on their behaviors or actions involving your business.</description></item><item><title>Branding experience</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/branding-experience/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/branding-experience/</guid><description>Relevant Notes ux-design Notes What is branding experience Brand experience encompasses subjective consumer responses in the form of sensations, feelings, thoughts, and reactions responses in response to brand-related stimuli.</description></item><item><title>Burnout is an organizational issue</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/burnout-organizational-issue/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/burnout-organizational-issue/</guid><description>Relevant Notes Reference The Burnout Conversation Is A Corporate Tool To Turn Your Suffering Into Marketing - by Ed Z - Ed Zitron&amp;rsquo;s Where&amp;rsquo;s Your Ed At Notes The reason why people burnout in companies is not solely about amount of workload.</description></item><item><title>Candidate red flags</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/candidate-red-flags/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/candidate-red-flags/</guid><description>Relevant Notes getting-hired interviews Notes 1 Arriving late without update Rude Dodge question about failures Want to leave current job because they are bored Asks questions for the sake of asking questions Highlights LinkedIn Talent Solutions 15 Interview Productivity Hacks &amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;</description></item><item><title>Case studies in UX design</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/case-study/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/case-study/</guid><description>Relevant Notes Notes Highlights Sahil Bishnoi on LinkedIn1 What was the project goal? Set up the context by explaining the problem / goal that your client or team is trying to achieve.</description></item><item><title>choose-perspective</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/choose-perspective/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/choose-perspective/</guid><description>Relevant Notes Notes Take a perspective that empowers you personally. Quotes and Insights &amp;ldquo;Different meanings can be assigned to the same events.</description></item><item><title>collector-fallacy</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/collector-fallacy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/collector-fallacy/</guid><description>Relevant Notes productivity learning-in-public Notes Fallacy: As you collect, your knowledge grows But what actually happens is that you don&amp;rsquo;t process and digest these notes Although a lengthy process, take time to convert these notes into ones you actually learn, know, and digest&amp;ndash;you don&amp;rsquo;t learn just by highlighting What we need to focus on is DEVELOP knowledge, not connect Highlights The Collector’s Fallacy • Zettelkasten Method The worst we could do is to pile up copies until the stack grows intimidatingly high, until it becomes unmanageable.</description></item><item><title>Content marketing</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/content-marketing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/content-marketing/</guid><description> Tags: #permanent-notes Relevant Notes writing-marketing-copy How-to editorial calendar Make it divided into: 70% standard, 20% moderately risky, 10% innovative Elements Submission date Publish date Title Target audience Writer Reviewer 70/20/10 category &amp;ldquo;In&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;out&amp;rdquo; Status Standardizing Creating lexicons Write it down Show alternatives Create an index</description></item><item><title>Design is political x Decolonizing design</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/decolonizing-design/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/decolonizing-design/</guid><description>Relevant Notes Notes Western ideologies have shaped our concepts of &amp;ldquo;preferable design&amp;rdquo;. Anything outside these Western preferences are seen as different or inferior.</description></item><item><title>Design Teams</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/design-teams/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/design-teams/</guid><description>Relevant Notes leadership in design work-culture Notes How to build a design team Work cultures &amp;amp; environments are different–we hire people that would complement the team.</description></item><item><title>Don't be afraid of failure</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/afraid-failure/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/afraid-failure/</guid><description> Relevant Notes career-advice feedback Notes Your good ideas are hidden under the bad ones Your first 50 attempts will be terrible, so go ahead and use them up Highlights</description></item><item><title>Emotions are contagious</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/emotions-contagious/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/emotions-contagious/</guid><description>Relevant Notes collective-effervesence Notes You feel the emotions around the people around you. Some examples of these are collective anxiety, Zoom fatigue, etc.</description></item><item><title>How to write better sentences</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/write-better-sentences/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/write-better-sentences/</guid><description>Relevant Notes Notes Be creative in writing. Play with the emotions of the readers such as fear, surprise, or their senses.</description></item><item><title>Make research accessible to the public</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/distilled-research-ecosystem/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/distilled-research-ecosystem/</guid><description>Relevant Notes Notes We often glorify complex and hard-to-understand articles. However, this idea that the &amp;ldquo;climb should be hard&amp;rdquo; is not progress, we are instead putting on research debt.</description></item><item><title>Should you send a thank you note?</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/ty-note/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/ty-note/</guid><description>Relevant Notes career-advice Notes TLDR; Yes. Highlights Thanks or no thanks? Sending a note1</description></item><item><title>Typography inclusivity &amp; accessibility</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/web-type-access/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/web-type-access/</guid><description>Relevant Notes References Webflow 101 crash course | Webflow University Notes Considerations Font legibility Ultra thin fonts are difficult to read especially as paragraph Uneven weight distribution Text alignment Uneven rag in typography, example in centered text Alt caps All caps has more cognitive load Consider use when text is too long Underlines Standard: It is a hyperlink Consider something else for emphasis Contrast Use contrast checkers Higher contrast</description></item><item><title>What works for social does not work for organic</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/facebook-v-organic/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/facebook-v-organic/</guid><description>Relevant Notes marketing-tooling Notes What works for social does not work for organic. It&amp;rsquo;s important to search for the keywords that are good for both/ either.</description></item><item><title>When we have a problem, we tend to go with solutions that involve adding something than taking something existing away</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/adding-than-taking/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/adding-than-taking/</guid><description>Relevant Notes hanlon Notes Highlights When faced with a problem, people tend to select solutions that involve adding new elements rather than taking existing components away.</description></item><item><title>Work Culture</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/work-culture/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/work-culture/</guid><description>Tags: #permanent-notes Relevant Notes leadership positive-leadership psychological-safety Concepts Burnout is an organizational issue Notes Good vs bad work culture Good work culture involves psychological-safety Tools for enhancing connection between team Figma Design Team Trading Cards Highlights Good vs bad work culture Bad work culture Signs company is badly managed1 Employees are fleeing.</description></item><item><title>Workplace equity</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/workplace-equity/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/workplace-equity/</guid><description>Relevant Notes leadership Notes Distribute tasks between men and women There is a societal expectation for women to volunteer more in non-promotable tasks.</description></item><item><title>Zettelkasten</title><link>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/zettelkasten/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://garden.chloeabrasada.online/notes/zettelkasten/</guid><description> Relevant Notes learning learning-thinking-communicating 09042021 PKM &amp;amp; Idea Emergence Notes Essentially writing FAST notes, on note cards, in your own words, one idea per card, with a link to another card Don&amp;rsquo;t fall into the collector&amp;rsquo;s fallacy Highlights</description></item></channel></rss>